annsummers.com 2017-11-19

# Ann Summers | Privacy Policy

Ann Summers is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors and customers of our website. This privacy policy explains how we collect, store and use personal data about you when you browse www.annsummers.com (the "Website"), shop with us or otherwise provide your personal data to us. It provides you with details about the types of personal data that we collect from you, how we use your personal data and the rights you have to control our use of your personal data.

You must read this privacy policy carefully and we recommend that you print and retain a copy for your future reference. By accessing, browsing or otherwise using this Website, you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy in its entirety. If you do not agree to this privacy policy in its entirety, you must not use this Website.

### Who We Are

This website is owned and operated by Ann Summers Ltd. Ann Summers Ltd is a company registered in England and Wales (company registration number 1034349) whose registered office is at Gold Group House, Godstone Road, Whyteleafe, Surrey, CR3 0GG. Our registered VAT number is 210 551 810, Please note our VAT rate is 20%. Unless we say otherwise, we use the terms "Ann Summers", "AnnSummers.com", “Knickerbox”, "we", "us" and “our” on this page to refer to Ann Summers Ltd (including throughout the Website Privacy Policy and Website Terms & Conditions).

If you want to ask us anything (whether about our privacy policy, our products and services, this website, any of our terms and conditions or otherwise), then please [click here to contact us](https://www.annsummers.com/contactus).

Telephone number: 

#### 0333 440 6969

### Over 18s Only

We do not and will not knowingly collect information from any person under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you must not use this Website or submit any personal data. Due to the nature of some of our products, you must be over 18 to use and shop on our website.

### The Personal Data We Collect About You

When you make purchases from Ann Summers (including purchases made in-store, over the phone, via our catalogue order forms, at an Ann Summers party or this Website) we may collect the following personal data about you:

  * your name, age and sex; 
  * your billing and delivery postal addresses, phone, and e-mail details; 
  * where you have registered with us, your user name and password; 
  * where you place an order with us, your payment card details; 
  * your communication and shopping preferences; 
  * your browsing and online shopping activities; and 
  * your date of birth.

We may also collect some or all of the above personal data about you when you access and browse this Website or any third party microsite (as described below), including when you sign up to receive Ann Summers newsletters. We may also collect some or all of this personal data from third parties who have your consent to pass your details to us.

We do not sell or pass any of your data to any third parties for marketing purposes.

### How We May Store And Use Your Information

Ann Summers (and third party data processors/services acting on our behalf) may collect, store and process your personal data:

  * To make this Website available to you and to provide you with content which is tailored to your individual tastes; 
  * To maintain any registered account that you hold with us 
  * With your agreement, to contact you (including by e-mail and SMS) about promotional offers and products and services which we think may interest you and for customer satisfaction and market research purposes;
  * To provide our goods and services to you and for associate purposes, including verifying your identity; 
  * For research, analysis, testing, monitoring, risk management and administrative purposes; 
  * For any related purposes, or where we have a legal right or duty to use or disclose your information (including for crime and fraud prevention and related purposes). 

We also process your payment card details in order to complete any purchase that you make through this Website and, in certain instances, disclose your personal data to third party credit reference agencies to perform credit checks against you. 

In addition, we may collect anonymous details about visitors to our Website for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes. However, no single individual will be identifiable from the anonymous details that we collect for these purposes.

Our web site may also use the SessionCam web site recording service. SessionCam is a product that has been developed by SesionCam LTD, SessionCam may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, page scrolling and any text keyed into website forms. The information collected does not include bank details or any sensitive personal data. The information collected is used to improve our website usability and is stored and used for aggregated and statistical reporting.

### Microsites

Ann Summers has partnered with certain trusted third parties to make available certain additional third party products, services and information to you, including:

<https://www.twitter.com/AnnSummers>

Each of these third party products and services can be accessed online through the relevant third party's "microsite". A microsite is a website that is owned and operated by Ann Summers or a third party but and can be accessed from links on the main Ann Summers Website. Alternatively, you can visit a microsite by clicking on the links above.

Please note that, although Ann Summers’ third party partners display Ann Summers branding on their respective microsites, Ann Summers does not own or operate any microsite and each microsite is governed by its own terms and conditions and privacy policy. Personal data that you provide or which are collected about you through a microsite will be used by the relevant third party in accordance with that microsite's terms and conditions and privacy policy. In some cases, third party microsite operators may disclose your personal data to us so that we may use them in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or concerns about the collection or use of your personal data collected through any microsite, you should contact the relevant third party microsite operator using the contact information specified in their privacy policy.

Please note that there are a number of Ann Summers imitators and resellers online. Please do not buy from these websites. They are not official stockists and not governed by our Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy. We can also not guarantee they are selling genuine Ann Summers products or have gone through our stringent testing policy and quality assurance. 

### Email Newsletters

You can subscribe to our newsletter where you will receive emails about products, offers, competitions, news, Ann Summers Parties and much more. 

### Targeted Updates and Marketing

If you have agreed that we can contact you for marketing purposes we may send you emails and other communications relating to products and services which we think will be of interest and relevance to you as an individual. We do this by monitoring the browsing and online shopping habits of customers and providing them with information on products they have viewed and related products.

### Cookies

This Website uses cookies to collect information about you. Cookies are small data files which are placed on your computer or other device by this Website and which collect certain personal data about you. This enables us to tailor our service offering (including the Website) to provide you with products and services which are more relevant to your individual tastes. You may change your website browser settings to reject cookies, although please note that if you do this it may impair the functionality of the Ann Summers website. Ann Summers has relationships with carefully selected and monitored suppliers to assist in the delivery of a high quality website. Some of these suppliers may also set cookies during your visit in order to meet contractual obligations with Ann Summers (Supplier Cookies). Both Ann Summers and Supplier cookies do not store any personal information relating to you or your credit cards. We also use JavaScript to speed up your online shopping experience. For further information about cookies, including how to refuse cookies, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

### Changes in Laws Regarding Cookies

From May 2011, the laws regarding the use of cookies changed to prevent the storing of cookies without the user’s permission. Ann Summers fully supports this ruling, and have worked to bring this use in line. By using this site you are accepting our use of cookies unless you choose to reject them as stated above.

For more information about cookies, please visit this independent site. (Ann Summers is not responsible for the content of external sites.)

### Security

We use Internet standard encryption technology ("SSL" or "Secure Socket Layer" technology) to encode personal data that you send to us when placing an order through the Website. To check that you are in a secure area of the Website before sending personal data to us, please look at the bottom right of your website browser and check that it displays an image of a closed padlock or an unbroken key However, please note that whilst we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal data that you provide to us, no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed secure. Consequently, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any personal data that you transfer over the Internet to us.

If you are using a computer or terminal in a public location, we recommend that you always log out and close the website browser when you complete an online session for your security. In addition we recommend that you take the following security measures to enhance your online safety:

  * Keep your account passwords private. Remember, anybody who knows your password may access your account. 
  * When creating a password, we recommend use at least 8 characters. A combination of letters and numbers is best. We recommend you do not use dictionary words, your name, email address, or other personal data that can be easily obtained. We also recommend that you frequently change your password. You can do this by going to ‘My Account’ and clicking ‘Change name, email or password’, 
  * Avoid using the same password for multiple online accounts.

### Spoof/false Emails

We will never ask you to confirm any account or credit card details via email. If you receive an email claiming to be from annsummers.com asking you to do so, please ignore it and do not respond.

### You have the following rights:

  * the right to ask what personal data that we hold about you at any time, subject to a fee specified by law (currently £10);
  * the right to ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal data that we hold about you free of charge; and 
  * the right to opt out of any marketing communications that we may send you.

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please contact our customer services department. However, if you wish to unsubscribe from e-mail marketing communications that we send you, you can most easily do this by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any e-mail newsletter we have sent to you.

### Third Party Sites

This Website contains links to other websites operated by third parties (including microsites, described above). Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the personal data that we collect through this Website and we cannot be responsible for personal data that third parties may collect, store and use through their website (including microsites). You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully.

### Internet Shopping Is Safe Accredited Retailer

Ann Summers is an ISIS accredited retailer and annsummers.com is verified as an ISIS compliant website.

### Updates to this Policy

This privacy policy was last updated in August 2017. Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates to this privacy policy.
